# **Curriculum Vitae**

## **PERSONAL DETAIL:**

Name: Moujza Fatima Zuhra

Nationality Pakistani

Date of Birth 26.07.1993

Marital Status Single

Father's Name Asghar Shah

Postal Address I-10/2, main railway road, house # 851 Islamabad

Telephone Number +92 3365831148

Email Address moujzaaqureshi@gmail.com

#### **OBJECTIVE:**

With a great ambition to advance my academic career in the field of Bio-medical Sciences, I am determined to become a globally renowned researcher. My goals are focused on academic achievements as well as to serve my country and humanity.

## **EDUCATIONAL DETAIL:**

Oct 2011-Sep 2015

Bachelor of Science (Hon.) Kohat University of Science & Technology

Biotechnology and Genetic Engineering Kohat, KPK, Pakistan

May 2011

FSC (Premedical) Pak-Aims School-College of Science & Technology

Higher Secondary Education Kohat, KPK, Pakistan

LANGUAGE SKILLS:

**English**: IELTS-6.5 Bands (Speaking; 6.5 Reading; 6.5 Writing; 6.0 Listening; 6.0)

German: A1 Level

#### **COMPUTER SKILL:**

Good computer savvy; MS-Office and searching scientific articles from search engines Sciencedirect.com, Pubmed.com.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE:**

January 2016- March 2016 Genetic Resource Center Rawalpindi, Pakistan

- Learned DNA Extraction,
- > PCR for Delta 508 Mutation &JAK2 Mutation.
- > Prenatal diagnosis of Thalassemia, Trisomy and Duchene Muscular Dystrophy
- Chorionic Villus Sampling (CVS) and amniocentesis Qualitative PCR for HBV & HCV, HCV PCR & Genotyping, PCR for Malaria, Sex determination, Thalassemia & Xmn-I Genotyping.

### Mar 2013- May 2014

Shaukat Khannum Memorial Cancer Hospital & Research Center Rawalpindi, Pakistan

- Supported SKMCH&RC in its marketing endeavors
- Raised awareness about cancer among people by organizing campaigns
- > Served in fund raising for the hospital as a responsibility to fight against cancer

Nov 2012- Apr 2013
Voice of Youth Organization
Kohat, Pakistan

- Worked as a youth Representative of Kohat region
- > Organized & managed different educational events, seminars, conferences and training sessions for the awareness of young generation
- Coordination with different organizations.

## **REFEREE:**

Dr. Muhammad Jamil Associate Professor Department of Biotechnology and Genetic Engineering Kohat University of Science and Technology Tel: +92-922375560 and +92/3005286949

E-mail: jamilkhattak@yahoo.com

Dr. Noor Muhammad Assistant Professor Department of Biotechnology and Genetic Engineering Kohat University of Science and Technology

Tel: +92-3028081457

E-mail: noormwazir@yahoo.com